{
    "subject": "resource/Eden's_Bowy",
    "predicate": "property/genre",
    "object": "resource/Adventure",
    "human_readable": "Eden's Bowy is an Adventure.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7642992734909058,
            "question": "Is Eden's Bowy a fantasy story?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7551514506340027,
            "question": "Would Eden's Bowy appeal to readers who enjoy exciting adventures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6492276191711426,
            "question": "Could Eden's Bowy involve quests and magical creatures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6082664132118225,
            "question": "What genre is Eden's Bowy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4800000786781311,
            "question": "What is the main plot or theme of Eden's Bowy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4649229347705841,
            "question": "Who are the main characters in Eden's Bowy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41265884041786194,
            "question": "Where does the story of Eden's Bowy take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3768805265426636,
            "question": "What kind of challenges might the characters in Eden's Bowy face?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2851659953594208,
            "question": "What is the overall tone or mood of Eden's Bowy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27406540513038635,
            "question": "Can you imagine any movie adaptations based on Eden's Bowy?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eden's Bowy is an Adventure.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6406_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the overall tone or mood of Eden's Bowy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6406_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of challenges might the characters in Eden's Bowy face?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6406_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does the story of Eden's Bowy take place?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6406_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6406_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6406_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6406_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6406_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6406_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6406_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6406_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6406_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6406_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6406_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "The triple to be evaluated is \"Eden's Bowy is an Adventure\". Based on the provided context information, here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because while the reviews mention that Eden's Bowy is a \"fantasy/adventure series\", they also describe it as having elements of action and comedy, indicating that it may not be solely an adventure genre."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents describe Eden\u2019s Bowy as a fantasy/adventure series, which supports the statement that Eden's Bowy is an adventure."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information provided contains multiple reviews of Eden's Bowy, but none of them describe the anime as an adventure. In fact, review 1 and 3 mention that it has a \"great storyline\" and is perfect for fans of action and adventure genres with a sub-genre of hunting, which suggests that it may have elements of adventure, but this does not necessarily mean that the entire series is classified as an adventure.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}